Hello, hello friends,
hello friends, today we will talk
about a company about which people have little
knowledge. Yes, this company
is ICICI Lombard Insurance Company.
Friends, first of all, I
would like to know from you. Please tell me in the comments
which of our brothers are such
subscribers who have some
insurance company in their portfolio or
not.
Friends, till now I have designed portfolios of many people for
free and have
also checked them again. I have seen
that most of my brothers do not have
any insurance factor company in their portfolio,
which is a very wrong thing. So, such a
time is coming. Even today you must have read the news
that the Punjab Madras High Court has decided that
from September 1, there will be bumper-to-bumper
insurance of the vehicle. So, friends,
now the time is coming like it happens in America, it
happens in European countries that
insurance is very important for you.
What will happen when insurance is very important?
Everyone will insure. If everyone will insure, then
who will benefit from it?
It will be the companies that do insurance. So,
friends, if any brother does
not have an insurance company in his portfolio, then please tell me.  Tell me by commenting.
Send me your portfolio. I will
give you the link
of your Telegram channel in the description as well. I will
not take a single rupee from you without any reason. I only believe
that this is not a gambling house; this is a place for share market
investment. In this, those of you who
say that I will give you a tip, my friend, it will
increase so much, then brother, you should take it from them only.
I do not have any tips. I cannot tell
you whether this stock increased by 5% yesterday, it will increase by 6% tomorrow or it will fall by 5%. I can only tell you in that sense that like you make an FD in the bank, you make it for a
period of one year, it is for at
least six months. Now if you make an
FD today for six months, then after 6 minutes you
go and ask
how much has our money increased in the bank? Now, what was the principal
amount and how much interest did we get? What was our
problem? Profit has become our problem.
So, those who want to do this, I
welcome them wholeheartedly. They should join me and
join me. I can guarantee them
that not only FD, I will get them returns many times more than FD.
But those who want  To
become a millionaire in one day, to become a millionaire in two days, so
please this place is
not right for them, they should look for somewhere else
because by doing so they will suffer loss and they will throw
me out, I do not
want them to abuse me or suffer loss, so
friends, we are talking about this, I will
not make it long by belittling you, let's
talk about it in short, I will talk from there that the
company which has
increased by five percent today, its share has
increased by five percent, if we look at the weekly, then
according to this, five to six percent, today it has
increased by only six percent, if we look at the two
monthly charts in a week, then friends, you will see
that even in one month, the passenger road has
increased by six percent, friends, after this, look
here and friends, if you see this near, there is a
rise of 22 percent, if you make an FD, then you will
keep it in the biggest bank in India, friends,
you will not get more than six percent or seven percent of
interest anywhere in the country, friends,
in this you are getting an interest of 22.5%,
friends, and if we look at the three-year
prospective, friends, you have
fun remember friends, 3 years  The amount has
more than doubled, there is an increase of 107 percent,
friends. 3 years ago the share price was
Rs 607, today the price is at 1557. And friends, if we
look beyond this, we see that in the 15-year-old project,
in the five-year project, there is an
increase of 140 percent,
140 percent, whoever
invested money at that time has become a
millionaire today. And friends, let's
go even further and see
how much profit was made in such an investment,
friends, I click on it the most.
In such an investment, this 139
percent people have made money, friends, in
that,
friends, if you invest money every month,
choosing any share, choosing a good share,
it will cost money every month. You will definitely
buy in tips also, you will give that share at a medium price of Rs
250, you will sell that share at a higher price,
friends,
when you buy money, you will buy with investment, then
your profit will
increase so much, friends, that you will not be able to believe it.
Now friends, let's discuss a
little about the fundamentals of this sector and company.
Look friends,
this  The market worth Rs 66,894 crore is
not the last step of the apps company, but it is a
mid-cap company. Friends, if
we look at the taxes of this company, the biggest
speciality will be seen. Friends, this company is a debt-free
company. There is no debt on it. Sir,
friends, this company has not taken any loan.
And friends, if you look at it,
then the
question of the industry of Rs 987 is that Rs 1000 is doing well. It is
earning a lot of money.
DDL point five is four. Friends, and now
we move ahead, if we look at its revenue,
if we look at its growth, it is near. Sir,
friends, see, from Rs 17 to Rs 1000, the
cost is increasing. Rs 7500 crore, Rs 400
crore, Rs 10,000 crore, Rs 11060, Rs 1000 crore, Rs 12 now Rs
200 crore. Friends, looking at its profit,
and see, the graph is always
moving upwards. Earlier, it was Rs 11000, Rs
1149 crore, then after that it became Rs 11-12 crore,
now it has become Rs 15 crore.  Friends,
this company is such that if you buy it once and
keep it in your portfolio, you will forget it, then
after 3 years you will remember it, so
my message to you friends is that
now let's talk about some of its
technicals, we have checked the fundamentals, the
technicals give, see its
black line to dead, this is the line in,
see where has it taken support, then
it has judged
that it is taking support here, one day there is support
and it is showing support, yes it is taking support,
all this is flying, it is
taking support again and again, now whenever you see it, it does
not let it fall from anywhere, whenever you
see that it does not let it fall anywhere, the
share price does not go down, it immediately
takes support, see, the morning
fog started appearing from all four sides, but the share immediately took support,
see, it has been given a break from thieves,
fifty rupees and the price in 2001 was Rs.
1447.19 paise, I believe that
it will not break this price quickly,
you should note this, it will
not break this price quickly, and I have
a request to you, keep these shares
in your portfolio  Do keep it and
tell me by commenting whether you have shares in your portfolio
or not and since when and
in what quantity, I would love to hear it
and friends I want to tell you one more thing
if any brother wants to join his
portfolio, if
he feels that he is
not earning in his portfolio, he is not enjoying it, then
he can take my help, I will
not charge you even ₹1 for this, I am
telling the truth, my Radhe thing is
that my friends, my brothers and sisters, do not suffer any
loss, they should earn this, they should
earn this, but
again the retailer is a small man, he is not
able to do anything, so friends I will tell you about it,
look
now I want you to keep this oil with you, your
portfolio should always remain, you should
earn money in it and you should get profit in future,
if you liked my video then please
like, share
and comment on that video, friends I have
only one request to you that if you
keep this oil in your portfolio and if
you keep it in your portfolio for 1 year, then
it will be beneficial for you  2000 plus, yes, it will
show a price above two thousand, this
is my guarantee to you, but for that you will have to
wait a little, for that you will have to
wait for one year, yes for one year, so you
must add it to your portfolio
and when the price of rain in one year becomes 2000,
then tell me by commenting, sir, whether what
you said turned out to be right or wrong,
give it to me or taste it.